betakit.com 2012-12-26

# BetaKit » Privacy Policy

Postmedia Network Canada Corp. and its affiliated and subsidiary entities, including Postmedia Network Inc. (“Postmedia Network”, “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy and safeguarding your personal information. This Privacy Statement describes how we may collect, use and disclose personal information. This Privacy Statement applies to any personal information we collect or receive about you, from any source. However, it does not apply to personal information that we collect, use or disclose for journalistic purposes.  
By submitting your personal information, subscribing to our services or products or using our websites, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement. Please check back periodically as this Privacy Statement may be amended from time-to-time and applies to all Postmedia Network divisions.

WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?

‘Personal information’ means information about an identifiable individual. Examples of personal information that we may collect, use and disclose include your contact information (name, address, phone number or email address), your billing information (credit card number or banking information), and other information that you may provide to us. Personal information does not include publicly available information or your business contact information.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT? TO WHOM DO WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION?

In most cases, we will collect personal information directly from you when you purchase or interact with us about a product or service that we offer or provide (for example, when you subscribe to a newspaper or when you email us or contact us through our website). Occasionally, we may collect personal information from a third party based on your consent or as otherwise permitted by law.  
We identify the purposes for which we may collect, use and disclose your personal information at the time that we collect such information. Such purposes include providing and delivering products or services to you, responding to your inquiries, and internal business purposes such as administering or improving our website. We obtain your consent for such purposes at or before the time that we collect, use or disclose your personal information, except where permitted or required by law.  
Postmedia Network’s divisions and affiliates may share personal information with each other in order to fulfill the purposes that you have consented to. We may also share your personal information with third party service providers as necessary for them to provide services on our behalf. Some service providers may be located outside of Canada where personal information may be subject to the laws of those jurisdictions.  
We may disclose personal information to a potential purchaser in connection with the sale of some or all of the business of Postmedia Network, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.

HOW DO WE RETAIN AND SAFEGUARD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We retain personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and as permitted or required by law. We have implemented physical, organizational, contractual and technological security measures to protect your personal information from loss or theft, and unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

HOW DO WE MONITOR OUR WEBSITES?

Our websites may place and access cookies when you visit our websites. A cookie is a small data file that websites commonly write to your computer. A cookie file contains information that can identify you each time you visit the website. Our websites use cookies as a way to measure website activity and traffic patterns. We may use third-party vendors and advertising networks to serve advertisements on our websites. Such third parties may place and access cookies on your browser, including for the purpose of delivering tailored advertisements to you. That activity is subject to such third-parties’ policies and terms. You may choose to set your computer to reject cookies if you desire. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features available on our websites.

From time to time, we collect certain usage information from our servers that relates to the use of our websites. We use this information to improve our website, for example by enhancing pages or features that are visited frequently, and on occasion we may share this information with our affiliates or other third party companies to provide them with an indication of the amount of interest in our website for advertising purposes and to help us plan for technical improvements.

HOW CAN YOU ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We will make available to you any personal information that we have collected, used or disclosed, upon your written request, to the extent permitted by law. We will attempt to respond to your written request within thirty (30) days. We will advise you in writing if we cannot meet your request within this time limit.

CONTACT US

Our Privacy Officers are accountable for our compliance with this Privacy Statement and applicable privacy law. All comments, questions, concerns or complaints regarding your personal information should be forwarded to our Privacy Officers as follows:

BY EMAIL:
